<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyMovieApp</string>

    <!-- Movie 1-->
    <string name="title1">Oppenheimer</string>
    <string name="description1">
        Oppenheimer is a 2023 epic biographical thriller film written,
        co-produced, and directed by Christopher Nolan.
        It follows the life of J. Robert Oppenheimer, the American theoretical
        physicist who helped develop the first nuclear weapons during World War II. Based on the 2005
        biography American Prometheus by Kai Bird and Martin J. Sherwin, the film dramatizes Oppenheimer\'s
        studies, his direction of the Los Alamos Laboratory and his 1954 security hearing. Cillian Murphy stars as Oppenheimer,
        alongside Robert Downey Jr. as the United States Atomic Energy
        Commission member Lewis Strauss. The ensemble supporting cast includes Emily Blunt, Matt Damon,
        Florence Pugh, Josh Hartnett, Casey Affleck, Rami Malek, and Kenneth Branagh.
    </string>
    <string name="category1">History</string>
    <!-- Movie 2 -->
    <string name="title2">How to Train Your Dragon</string>
    <string name="description2">
       How to Train Your Dragon is a 2025 American fantasy adventure film and a live-action remake
        of the 2010 animated film, itself loosely based on the 2003 novel by Cressida Cowell.
        Produced by DreamWorks Animation and Marc Platt Productions, the film was written and directed by Dean DeBlois,
        who co-wrote and directed the animated films. It stars Mason Thames, Nico Parker,
        Gabriel Howell, Julian Dennison, Bronwyn James, Harry Trevaldwyn,
        Peter Serafinowicz, and Nick Frost, with Gerard Butler reprising his role as Stoick
        the Vast from the animated films.
    </string>
    <string name="category2">Animation</string>

    <!-- Movie 3 -->
    <string name="title3">Blade Runner 2049</string>
    <string name="description3">
        Blade Runner 2049 is a 2017 neo-noir science fiction film directed by Denis Villeneuve.
        A sequel to the 1982 film Blade Runner, it stars Ryan Gosling as "K", a replicant Blade Runner
        who unearths a secret that could destabilize society. His journey leads him to former Blade Runner Rick Deckard (Harrison Ford).
        The film explores themes of identity, memory, and the nature of humanity in a visually stunning dystopian future.
    </string>
    <string name="category3">Sci-Fi</string>

    <!-- Movie 4 -->
    <string name="title4">Final Destination: Bloodlines</string>
    <string name="description4">
        Final Destination: Bloodlines continues the chilling legacy of the franchise where a group
        of individuals escapes a deadly event—only to be hunted one by one by death itself.
        With new characters, intense premonitions, and inventive fatal sequences, this installment
        delves deeper into the eerie pattern that fate never forgets.
    </string>
    <string name="category4">Horror</string>
</resources>